question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it's entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion "
                 "in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal "
                 "substances without revealing themselves.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Ananas' is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
